[Music]
[Música]
those who are not going to be
los que no se van a pegar mucho tiempo
on YouTube for long It seems that they are from the
en YouTube Parece ser que son los de la
TV factory now manufacturer And they
fábrica de la tele ahora fabricante Y es
are already making their little space on
que ya están haciendo su huequito en
Spanish television as they did
televisión española como ya batis
a few months ago I
sinamos de hace unos cuantos meses yo
think it is not missing because
creo que no falta por falta por
the date is yet to be confirmed But well for now
confirmar la fecha Pero bueno de momento
what is confirmed is worth It seems
lo que hay confirmado vale Parece ser
that Spanish television La Sobremesa is
que televisión española la sobremesa se
called the program like in the afternoon
llama el programa de como por la tarde
that time slot Sobremesa Sobremesa no at the
ese horario sobremesa sobremesa no de
moment Belén Esteban and María
momento está Belén Esteban y María
Patiño are collaborators and it is not known
Patiño de colaboradora y no se sabe
who else But from the environment it is not like we
quién más Pero del entorno ni que
were it is a program presented by
fuéramos es un programa presentado por
Mark Giro that we have already seen that in
Mark giro que ya hemos visto que en los
recent years we have seen that they have
últimos años hemos visto que tienen
a lot of relationship with him no and with the
bastante relación con él no y con el
world of the TV factory and
mundo de la fábrica de la tele y
collaborations and so on no and and it is going to
colaboraciones y demás no y y va a
compete in the time slot with Ana Rosa with
competir en el horario con Ana Rosa con
Son Soles directly and evidently it
son soles directamente y evidentemente
will be a magazine of Crónica social HM
será un magazín de Crónica social HM
as we have talked about these days more like
como hemos hablado estos días más like
we are talking about
estamos hablando de la televisión
Spanish television Look there is a set up in networks
española Mira hay una montada en redes
with this subject or rather I think that
con este tema o sea yo creo que
monopolized is also another of the topics of the
acaparado también es otro de los temas
day eh Because of course  Belen has
del día eh Porque claro belen ha
reacted to all this news Margo,
reaccionado a todas estas noticias Margo
yes, now we see it, it was brought out by
lo Sí ahora lo vemos lo ha sacado un
a Catalan media outlet, the issue of Margo,
medio un medio Catalán el tema de Margo
whether he has accepted the proposal, whether he has
que si él ha aceptado la propuesta que
not accepted the proposal, of course, in the
si no ha aceptado la propuesta claro al
end, manufacturers, eh, and Mar Giro go hand in
final fabricantes eh Y Mar giro van de
hand, in fact, a character from Sálvame
la mano de hecho personaje de sálvame
has gone there to the show that Mar has on her
han ido Ahí al show que tiene mar en su
program in Catalonia and Pablo, eh, that is,
programa de Cataluña y Pablo eh o sea
José Pablo, president of
José Pablo presidente de televisión de
Spanish radio and television, goes hand in hand
radio televisión española va de la mano
with manufacturers, that is, now everyone
con fabricantes o sea ahora todos todo
is starting to fit together all the pieces of the
empiezan a encajar todas las piezas del
pule. What's happening, obviously, that program
pule Qué pasa evidentemente ese programa
in which it seems that the dispute comes
en el que parece que la disputa viene
more because Belén and Patiño will be alone
más por van a estar Belén y Patiño solas
and the rest. What's happening and
y el resto Qué qué es lo que pasa y la
people are already like, if the whole lot doesn't go,
gente ya está es que si no va el lote
I don't know what it is, that being on
completo yo no sé qué es que al estar en
Spanish television it's going to be much
televisión española va a ser mucho más
weaker in terms of content, it's that we
flojo a nivel de contenido es que
want the same thing, of course, everyone is complaining,
queremos lo mismo claro todos son quejas
if they're not there because they're not there, if they're there
si no están porque no están si están
because it's going to be more sweetened, if
porque va a estar más edulcorado si
then everyone goes,
entonces est van todos
eh. What happens is that maybe Belén
eh Lo que pasa es que a lo mejor Belén
Esteban and María Patiño are like the
Esteban y María Patiño son como las
regulars,
fijas
let's say.  eh Yes in fact there have already been some
digamos eh Sí de hecho ya ha habido unas
knowing glances that speak for
miradas Cómplices que hablan por sí
themselves no but well I don't know look it
solas no pero pues no lo sé fíjate es
says Belén Esteban and María Patiño and
que dice Belén Esteban y María Patiño y
more people from the universe a kiss Consuelo
más gente del universo un beso Consuelo
that Ray has given us there I hope you had a
que nos ha hecho una Ray por ahí Espero
great time
que hayáis estado pasándolo muy bien
this
esta
afternoon I understand with that it will be like
tarde yo entiendo con eso que será como
rotating realize that Javi de hoyo
rotando date cuenta que Javi de hoyo
is also on Spanish television
Está también en televisión española
working of course they are from the heart yes
trabajando clo claro están de corazón sí
who else I tell you Marina Matamoros no
quién más te digo Marina Matamoros no
Matamoros at the moment nothing no of such a
Matamoros de momento nada no de de tal
host they are going to meet Terelu
[__] se van a encontrar con la terelu
in the end
al final
no well well no well look No because
no pues pues no pues fíjate No porque
Terelu is no longer there right now she is not
terelu ya no está ahora mismo no está
doing anything on Spanish television
haciendo nada en televisión española la
Terelu that I Terelu from the heart I well
terelu que yo terelu de corazón yo bueno
in mañaneros she is not unless they continue from the
en mañaneros no está a no ser que sigan
heart she had the problem but she came back not
corazón tuvo el problema pero volvió no
in the in the heart this one didn't have
en el en el de corazón este no tuvo
problems
problemas
mañaneros and from the heart Well let's see she's
mañaneros y en de corazón Pues a ver no
not always she's usually
está ves no está siempre a ver suele
has problems in general it's that Ah
tener problemas en general es que Ah
but it was because she returned to tele5 it was
pero fue porque se volvió a tele5 fue
because they started to  the
porque le empezaron a volver a surgir
sister's little things come up again, the nephew, I don't
las cositas de la hermana el sobrino no
know, I don't know how much and he started with the
sé que no sé cuánto y empezó con el
Tele5 jerk again and that really did
mamono de tele5 otra vez y eso ya sí que
n't go down well on Spanish television,
no gustó en televisión española
that's it, that's what's happening,
eso es eso es qué es lo que pasa que
look at me in the face of this and it's the way things
mira a mí ante esto y es las cosas como
are,
son
H, something's going on, it's the key and they haven't
H algo pasa es la clave y no se han
spoken out today, something's going on, it's the key
pronunciado hoy algo pasa es la clave
to confirm everything and more that it has to
para confirmar todo y más que tenga que
do with the factory, with the manufacturers, you
ver con la fábrica con con fabricantes
know, and they haven't said absolutely anything
sabes y no han dicho absolutamente nada
today, if it had been all this, man, it makes
hoy si hubiera sido todo esto hombre
sense and obviously it will be
tiene sentido y evidentemente se
confirmed, but if it hadn't been like that,
confirmará pero si no hubiera sido así
something's going on, he would have thrown out some
algo pasa ya hubiera tirado alguna
hints, something that he didn't do, but I'm
indirecta cosa que no ha hecho pero me
surprised that they haven't put
me sorprende que no que no hayan puesto
anything, they haven't put anything on the subject today. I
nada no han puesto nada del tema hoy Yo
think it's because, uh, point number
creo que es porque eh el punto número
one, it's known that something's going on, it comes
uno se sabe que algo pasa viene
directly
directamente
from already, it's already known who it is, something's going on,
de ya ya se sabe quién es el de algo
so if he gives information that they
pasa entonces si da una información que
are agreeing on it confidentially,
la están acordando con confidencialidad
uh, Well, of course, it's going to be a bit ugly, it's not
no eh Pues claro Va a ser un poco feo no
going to be a bit ugly, but
va a estar un poco feo pero aparte
also because it's not, it won't be
también porque no est no estará todavía
finished yet, it's going to be closed. It will also go away,
terminado de de cerrar Se irá también
realize that, of course, uh,
date cuenta que también claro Eh
so what's going on, have it?  YouTube I mean, not even if we
entonces qué pasa ten y YouTube o sea ni
were what because they're going to divide it
que fuéramos qué porque van a dividir cl
obviously if they're going to but of course I do
evidentemente si van a pero claro yo lo
n't know what But how What to divide what's
que no sé que Pero cómo Que a dividir
going on with not even if we were
qué es lo que pasa con ni que fuéramos
really that it's the same schedule No of
realmente que es el mismo horario No
course it's divide and conquer I don't know
claro es que es divido y vencerás no sé
at this point is that I don't know I mean I do
yo en este punto es que no lo sé o sea
n't really know
no sé realmente se se están barajando
so many options are being considered that until
tantas opciones que hasta que televisión
Spanish television confirms that I think Today is
española confirme que yo creo Hoy
tomorrow Thursday I think
estamos a mañana jueves yo creo que el
Monday of next week there will be there will be
lunes de la semana que viene habrá habrá
email for a call or something or a
email para convocatoria o algo o rueda
press conference because
de prensa ya porque ya presentándolo la
Marta Riesco is already presenting it in the
Marta riesco al
end of course Sálvame in the end is being
finala claro el sálvame al final se
presented by Marta Riesco how do I
queda presentado por Marta riesco cómo
know how how marola Marta Mola more than
se cómo cómo marola Marta Mola más de a
me Marta move it move it in the street by
mí Marta muévela muévela en la calle que
the way a kiss Marta is the
por ciertoo un beso Marta es la
presenter of course and Javi will be host
presentadora claro e Javi serán [__]
How clear you go Like that you go like that If
Cómo claro vas Así vas así Si está la
María Patiño is in the other but come on I
María Patiño en el otro pero vamos yo
think It's that I think that from the
creo Es que yo creo que desde el
beginning it's very obvious that they haven't
principio es muy obvio que ellos no han
taken the YouTube thing I had as something eh with
tomado lo de youtu tuve como algo eh con
thoughts of  this this is going to be
pensamientos de este este va a ser
our future they have it there as you
nuestro futuro ellos lo tienen ahí como
know like something while like well
sabes como algo de mientras como bueno
listen to me they usually have 15,000
escúchame suelen tener 15000
viewers on average every afternoon
espectadores de media todas las tardes
which is not bad they maintain it neither
que no está mal que lo mantienen ni
go up nor down well yes they have gone up
suben ni baj subido Bueno sí han subido
now really eh with Anabel
ahora en verdad eh con lo de Anabel
Pantoja in the last few days they have gone down
Pantoja en los últimos días han sub
clearly with Anabel with Anabel
claro con lo de Anabel con lo de Anabel
of course they have had peaks of 17 18 But
claro han tenido picos de 17 18 Pero
before Well also It's true that
antes Bueno también Es verdad que
we come from a very weak winter not
venimos del Invierno que muy flojo no
Christmas which is very weak and the
las navidades que son muy flojas y el
beginning of January which is very weak on
principio de enero que es muy flojo en
all the YouTube channels and they were
todos los canales de YouTube y estaban
with less than 10,000 some days No but I do
con menos de 10,000 algunos días No pero
n't know I understand How how it was if it was
no sé ya enten Cómo cómo era si era
sustainable or not but
sostenible o no pero vamos de todas
anyways is that I think that what
maneras es que yo creo que ellos a lo
they aspire to they want a
que que ellos aspira que quieren una
television they want a television channel that
tele que quieren una cadena de tele que
YouTube of course I think look since it
youtu claro yo creo fíjate desde que
started or that we were I think that the
empezó ni que fuéramos yo creo que la
intention of Óscar Cornejo and Adrian
intención de de Óscar Cornejo y Adrian
Madrid
Madrid
and it was this and it was Spanish television
e era esta y era televisión española
they and José Pablo have a very good
ellos y José Pablo tiene muy buen la
relationship and  I think it's been an
relación y yo creo que ha sido una
investment of time. Look how we
inversión de tiempo de Mira cómo
work, we're a little more
funcionamos estamos un poquito más
reduced in terms of content, it's no longer
rebajados a nivel contenidos ya no es
like Save Me, which is good, good, we crossed
como sálvame que bueno bueno cruzábamos
all the red lines and here it's everything and
todas las líneas rojas y aquí de todo y
in the end they've achieved their goal, which
al final han conseguido su objetivo que
is to reach a public network and a
es llegar a una cadena pública y a una
national network, and eh, but now, of course,
cadena nacional y eh pero ahora claro
now comes the commotion of some going, others,
ahora viene el revuelo de unos van otros
no, this one, yes, this one, no, the other envies, the
no este sí este no el otro envidia el
other gets angry with one, the contract, eh, what
otro se enfada con uno el contrato eh Lo
the workers think, what
que piensan los trabajadores lo que
people think, if one goes like that, the
piensa la gente si una así que va el
other is that, of course, It works,
otro es que claro Es que esto funciona
yes, it's like that, then they're like, very
Sí es que es así entonces son como much
negatively, it's never going to be Save Me
negativamente nunca va a ser salvame
again, no, it's never going to be, let's go, not even a
otra vez no no va a ser nunca vamos ni
joke, it will be a man, it will be a little
de ni de coñima será hombre será un
heart program, it will be an in, to me,
programita del corazón será un en a mí
Margo, no, no, no, no, it's not like
el Margo no me no no no es como
Jorge, it's that Jorge, it's that there has
Jorge no es que Jorge es que Jorge
only been one and look now
solamente ha habido uno y fíjate ahora
with a super low profile, but I think that
de perfil super bajito pero yo creo que
the same one. It's fine, like that, you know that it has
el mismo Está bien así sabe que ha
had its boom, that it has had, eh, its success
tenido su auge que ha tenido eh su éxito
because I think that objectively, eh, you
porque yo creo que objetivamente eh te
may like it more later, apart from
puede luego gustar más al margen de
ideologies and everything I think he's the
ideologías y de todo creo que es el
best at what he does I think there's never been
mejor en lo suyo creo que no ha habido
anyone like Jorge who has that
Nadie como Jorge que se con esa
ability to transmit for better or for
capacidad de transmitir para bien o para
worse and to communicate not for me I think he
mal y de comunicar no para mí Yo creo
's the best eh And the save me stage we did
que es el mejor eh Y la etapa de salvame
n't see it die I try or rather I
nada la vimos morir Yo intento o sea
understand that people don't long for all that
entiendo que la gente no anhele todo eso
and and and and think that maybe they're going to
y y y y piensa que a lo mejor lo va a
see it reflected on Spanish television
ver reflejado en televisión española
but nothing more I think it will be us
pero nada más creo que seremos nosotros
no I think it will be us no
no yo creo que seremos nosotros no
Marina who will do the save me No what do
Marina los que haremos el sálvame No qué
people need well man Give me give me
necesita la gente pues hombre Dame dame
a little more time because it's
un poquito más de tiempo que me es que
clear there you have to be made of a lot of
claro ahí hay que estar hecho de una
muscle Give me a little more gym Give me a few more
pastita Dame un poco más de gimnasio
weeks Give me a month okay okay
Dame unas semanas Dame un mes vale vale
let's see Belén's reaction come on
vamos a ver la reacción de beln venga
come on what people tell me or I'm
venga qu la gente me dice o me alegro
very happy about what Why are you going to the one
muchísimo de qué Porque te vas a la un
Ah
Ah
published is that Listen I have the
publicado es que Escucha tengo el
phone that falls on me press people
teléfono que se me cae gente de prensa
are you a presenter
eres presentadora
why did you say My partner do you
la porque dijiste Mi compañero te
remember yes Well then nothing V when you
acuerdas sí Bueno pues nada V cuando te
leave when you leave Belén Well I don't know
vay cuando te vas Belén Pues yo no sé
anything and you don't  you're leaving here without my
nada y tú no te vas de aquí sin mi
permission
permiso
Oy Uy how
Oy Uy qué
beautiful I can't people
bonita Yo yo no puedo que la gente me
tell me hey I didn't understand why Let's
dice oye no la he entendido por qué A
see
ver
eh I think it's a way of can't Maybe
eh yo creo que es una manera de no puede
say what you want to say doesn't
A lo mejor decir lo que quiere decir no
even know where to go and Maria Patiño
sabe ni por dónde salir y María Patiño
plays with that irony of why are
juega con con esa esa ironía de por por
you leaving Belén knowing that she's
qué te vas Belén sabiendo que ella
also going to leave because That's very
también se va a ir porque Eso está
clear then and then valde peras
clarísimo entonces y luego valde peras
also with that irony of if my permission
también con esa ironía de si mi permiso
you don't leave I don't know it's that maybe we'll even
tú no te vas no sé es que incluso a lo
see
mejor vemos
eh I don't know valde peras also it's that I haven't
eh No sé a valde peras también es que no
understood it has been like it has been like
lo he entendido ha sido como ha sido
an anger because they have done
como como un cabreo porque han hecho
something or rather because it has been confirmed not
algo o sea porque se ha confirmado no
one I think it's when she published
una Yo creo que es cuando ha publicado
Look put the news from voice popoli I
Mira pon la noticia de de voz popoli Yo
think it comes from there that it has been it has
creo que viene de ahí que ha sido ha
coincided more or less at the time that
coincidido más o menos en la hora que
they published that I
han publicado eso
think yes but I haven't understood very well
creo sí pero no he entendido muy bien la
the reaction the truth is that I don't know
la reacción la verdad es que no no sé
how to interpret it how
cómo interpretarlo cómo lo interpretas
you interpret it I interpret it as that people
tú yo lo interpreto como que la gente
are upset on the networks it's that I have started
está mosca en redes es que me he puesto
reading comments before Look at
a leer antes comentarios Mira ficha
Esteban's profile and  place sea twist in the afternoons
Esteban y coloca mar giro en las tardes
to compete with Ana Rosa and San eh No,
para competir con Ana Rosa y San eh No
what time was it published? This
esta qué a qué hora se ha publicado Esta
is that I don't see, I don't see from afar, yes, at
es que no veo no veo de lejos ya sí a
5:15 but there is no other
las 5:15 pero no hay otra
after that, yes, it is an update, not at
después sí es una actualización no a la
half an hour, but she has not had
media hora pero es que ella no le ha
time to read the news or see
dado tiempo de leer la noticia ni de ver
the reactions on social networks, I mean, it seems
la reacciones en redes o sea es como que
to me like,
a mí me ha da la impresión como
how do I explain to you, like, obviously, let's
e cómo te explico como que evidentemente
see, it seems
a ver
to me that she
e a mí me ha da la impresión de que ella
had not confirmed that she was going to be a
no tenía confirmado que ella fuese a ser
presenter or that she was going there at
presentadora o que ella se fuera ahí a
one, like she did not have it confirmed,
la uno como que no lo tenía ella
like there is something, there are some
confirmado como que hay algo hay algunas
conditions that she has set for that
condiciones que ella ha puesto para eso
of Spanish television and they have
de televisión española y la han
confirmed it without completely clarifying the
confirmado sin terminar de aclarar las
conditions, something like that, it is because she has looked
condiciones algo así es porque ha mirado
at María like a diend, what have
a la María como diend que le han hecho
these bastards done to her that they sent me to
estos cabrones que me han mandado para
one, do you
la uno me
understand, something like that, I have seen, I do not know
entiendes algo así he visto yo no sé
how to
cómo
explain it to you, it is that of course and we are
explicarte es que claro y estamos
also talking about presenting, so
hablando también de presentar entonces
people, people, let's see, it is very spontaneous, come
la gente la gente a ver es mu espontánea
on, it is very natural, we have seen her a thousand
vener es muy natural la hemos visto mil
times reading on Sálvame and presenting, reading  that
veces leer en sálvame y presentar leer
your grace but of course we are
el que su gracia pero claro estamos
also talking I don't know a
hablando también no sé una televisión
public television a strip eh it's that I don't know I mean no I don't
pública una franja eh es que no lo sé O
know yes it is true that Ah
sea no no lo sé sí que es verdad que Ah
okay Ah that this is when well well
vale Ah que esto es cuando bueno bueno
no and not only
que no y no solamente televisión
Spanish television both Spanish television and
española tanto televisión española como
Antena 3 have broadcast images of
Antena 3 han han emitido imágenes de
Belén Esteban I mean on Antena 3 they have
Belén Esteban o sea en Antena 3 le han
taken away the Beto also that she was already very
quitado el Beto también que estaba ya
happy today in as if we were it's
contentísima hoy en ni que fuéramos es
heavy they have put have put have put
heavy han puesto han puesto han puesto
the stories but but it's that on the one they
las historias pero pero es que en la uno
put directly as if we were Ah of
ponen directamente ni que fuéramos Ah
course it's like we are already on the same
claro ya es como ya somos del mismo
team we don't give feedback
equipo no nos retroalimentamos empieza
a new era is beginning in this sense that
una nueva era en este sentido que me
seems good to me or that we have to make room we have to
parece bien o que hay que dar cavida hay
give we have to make room I mean I
que dar hay que dar cabida o sea te
want to tell you if there is news or if there is
quiero decir si hay una noticia o si hay
whatever it is we have to echo it and cite you
lo que sea hay que hacerse eco y citar
can't put some statements and
no puedes poner unas declaraciones y
below the source No Put the video I have
abajo la fuente No Pon el vídeo yo
always defended that with everything no
siempre eso lo he defendido con todo no
Well of course let's see No I'm not putting it it's that they
Bueno claro a ver No no estoy poniendo
are starting to movements and
es que están empezando a movimientos y
little things no and And this is a sign no that they
cositas no y Y esto es una señal no que
are placing the video of I mean but
están colocando el vídeo de o sea pero
it's that also  people are really
es que también la gente como que le ha
surprised that the
llama mucho la atención que salgan las
images of us are coming out as if we were on channel one and
imágenes de ni que fuéramos en la uno y
it's like, well they don't come out
es como pu pues no salen mía algunas
sometimes to see it attract attention it attracts
veces a ver llamar la atención llama la
attention because it's the first time I mean
atención porque es la primera vez O sea
but then because it's another channel it's that they
pero luego lo porque es otra cadena es
're very used to
que está muy acostumbrados a que de
suddenly a video of a youtuber coming out
repente salga un vídeo de un youtuber
without permission or whatever Well to my
sin permiso o lo que sea Bueno a mí en
honor the truth is Spanish television has
honor la verdad televisión española
always asked my permission but they do
siempre me me ha pedido permiso que ya
n't do it anymore because the last
no lo hacen porque yo le en la última
time I told them look I'm asleep at that
vez le dije mira yo estoy dormido a esa
time don't take anything I mean don't ask my
hora no cojáis nada O sea no me pidáis
permission anymore let them take whatever they want do
más permiso que coja lo que quiera a mí
n't bother me then when I put
no me deis la lata luego cuando yo ponga
something up you know it's what I always
algo ya está sabes es lo que siempre
say to all the channels but people of
digo a todas las cadenas pero la gente
course it's not the same as them putting up a video of
claro no es lo mismo que pongan un vídeo
yours not images of you or of other
tuyo no imágenes tuyas no o de otros
youtubers that they have put up on some
youtubers que han puesto en algunas
occasions As them putting up images from another
ocasiones A que pongan imágenes de otra
channel Of course because it's from another channel
cadena Claro porque es de otra cadena
then you can see how but being
entonces ahí ya se ve como pero al ser
a public television I mean when it's
una televisión pública o sea cuando es
Spanish television Telemadrid etc I mean
televisión española telemadrid etc o sea
for example you before it's very strange you can't really be
por ejemplo tú antes es muy raro tú no
strange  that you go see Tele5
puedes rarísimo que vayas a ver a tele5
do Seco of something that has been given
hacer Seco de algo que ha dado en
exclusively by Antena 3 or vice versa on
exclusiva Antena 3 o y viceversa en
private channels but when it is a
cadenas privadas pero cuando es una tele
public television, public television With permission and
pública la tele pública Con permiso y
with rights it does not have No qualms I mean no no it's not a
con derechos no tiene No tiene reparos O
problem with putting
sea no no no pasa nada por poner
images from other channels strange you are going to see
imágenes de otras cadenas raro vas a ver
something from Tele5 something but something like that and it is
algo de tele5 algo pero algo así y está
clear that they go hand in hand it is very
claro que van de la mano es que está
clear that they go hand in hand
clarísimo que que van de la mano
then we
entonces
will have to wait I think that
e habrá que esperar yo creo que ya
tomorrow Thursday Fridays usually
mañana jueves los viernes no suele salir
nothing confirmed comes out of this but
nada confirmado de esto pero la semana
next week we will have confirmation I
que viene ya tendremos confirmación yo
think of almost everything because you cannot
creo de de casi todo porque tampoco
leave people in this state
puedes dejar a la gente en este estado
of wings since they are whiter let's see
de alas ya que son más blanquitos a ver
if at least they walk without vetoes no and they
si por lo menos andan sin vetos no y
mention Rosio Carrasco convicted
mencionan rosio Carrasco condenada
Antonio David I don't know that on
Antonio David no sé qu en televisión
Spanish television Carrasco convicted
española Carrasco condenada
not news But there has
no noticia Pero ha estado ahí
supposedly been a person there who with with
supuestamente una persona que con
whatever she
con sea con
is convicted cannot
que esté condenada no puede pisar
supposedly step on a plate Well that is the
supuestamente un plato Bueno ese es el
manual not of the style that they have but I do not
manual no del estilo que tienen pero yo
know if Rosio Carrasco would have a
no sé si roso Carrasco tendría
criminal record because Of course if she has
antecedentes penales porque Claro si ha
been convicted I that I alone  fine Of
sido condenada yo que yo sol la multa
course yes if she has not been sentenced in the
Claro si si no ha sido condenada al
end to a year in prison there is no
final al año de prisión no hay
criminal record either I don't understand I don't
antecedentes penales tampoco no entiendo
know if this thing of having a fine a
no lo sé si esto de tener una multa un
criminal record I don't know but well
antecedente penal no lo sé pero bueno
that speaking of Spanish television
que que hablando de televisión española
no and linking the other subject with
no y hilando el otro tema con televisión
Spanish television as well and wait eye eye and eh
española también y espera ojo ojo e eh
the time slot that would obviously compete
la franja que competiría evidentemente
with Ana Rosa and with son soles is very
con Ana Rosa y con son soles está muy
well thought out because the promise is a
bien pensado porque la promesa es un
success eh the modern one works very well
éxito eh la moderna funciona muy bien
too I mean these types of soap operas
también o sea las este tipo de novelas
Come on I mean they work I know that you
Vamos o sea es que funcionan sé que tú
don't watch them I don't either but
no las ves yo tampoco pero
my it's going to win eh let's see without knowing about
mi va a ganar eh sea a ver sin saber lo
the promise no and all the roll This
de la promesa no y todo el rollo Este
but they are going to win they are going to take
pero van a ganar se van a llevar ellos
the after-dinner time they are sure to know how to make television
la sobremesa seguro van a saber hacer
better than Ana Rosa know how to make
televisión mejor que Ana Ros saber hacer
television better yes that yes win man
televisión mejor sí eso sí ganar hombre
the first few days by expectation but
los primeros días por expectación pero a
maybe then they go and watch television
lo mejor luego andan a ver televisiones
or it could be it could be that yes it could
o puede ser puede ser que sí puede ser
be that yes they are going to win they are going to
que sí pu ser que sí van a ganar van a
win
ganar
[Music]
[Música]